Mello, Michael; Papers apap287
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Research Files, 1800-2004; 7; 14 cubic ft.
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 3 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 1)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 4 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 2)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 5 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 6 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 7 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 8 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 9 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 10 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 11 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 12 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 13 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 11)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 14 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 15 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 9 (7-Research Files), Folder 13)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 16 of 19), 1972-1993 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 1)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 17 of 19), 1973-1993 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 2)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 18 of 19), 1973-1993 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - Relentless Dissents- Marshall Papers ( 19 of 19), 1973-1999 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - US Code Service, Crimes and Criminal Procedure, Undated (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - Mason v. Arizona, 1975 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts Board of Retirement v. Murgia, 1976 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - Matlock v. Rose, 1984 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - Maxwell v. Florida, 1991 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - May v. Anderson, 1953 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - Warren McCleskey (1 of 2), 1984-1987; 1991; Undated (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 11)
  - Warren McCleskey (2 of 2), 1984-1987; 1991; Undated (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - "McClesky v. Kemp'. Race, Capital Punishment, and the Supreme Court" by Randall L. Kennedy, 1988 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 13)
  - McCollom v. Bush, 1965 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 14)
  - McCorquodale v. Kemp, 1987 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 15)
  - McCrae v. Florida, 1987 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 16)
  - McDowell v. Dixon, 1988 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 17)
  - McDuffic v. Sellers-Bok, 1995 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 18)
  - McKeiver v. Pennsylvania, 1971 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 19)
  - Dock McKay, 1989-1990 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 20)
  - "The meaning and Nature of the Natural Law in Thomas Aquinas" by William E. May, 1977 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 21)
  - " Mechanical Jurisprudence" by Roscoe Pound, 1908 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 22)
  - "Meditation form a Feminist Perspective: Promise and Problems" by Janet Rifkin, 1984 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 23)
  - Medical Malpractice, 1960; 1967; 1982; 1988; Undated (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 24)
  - Meeks v. Dugger, 1991 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 25)
  - Memo in Support of an Act to Amend the Penal Law, Undated (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 26)
  - Memorandrum in Opposition to S. 600/ A. 1070- New York Lawyers Against the Death Penalty, 1989 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 27)
  - Meneses v. Florida, 1979 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 28)
  - "Merciful Juries: The Resilience of Jury Nullification" by Scheflin and Van Dyke, 1991 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 29)
  - Messer v. Florida, 1987 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 30)
  - Middleton v. Dugger, 1988 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 31)
  - " The Metaphor of Standing and the Problem of Self- Governance" by Steven L. Winter, 1987 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 32)
  - Middleton v. State/ Caldwell Claims, 1988 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 33)
  - Mikenas v. Dugger, 1988 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 34)
  - "Militarism, Male Dominance and Law: Feminist Jurisprudence as Oxymoron?" by Ann Scales, 1989 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 35)
  - "Mind's Opportunity: Birthing a Postructuralist Feminist Jurisprudence" by Marie Ashe, 1987 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 36)
  - Minimum Statutory Ages for the Death Penalty- Eighth Edition by Victor Streib, 1988 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 37)
  - "Minors' Competence to Consent to Abortion" by Catherine C. Lewis, 1987 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 38)
  - Missouri v. Simmons, 1997 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 39)
  - Missouri v. Wilkins, 1987 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 40)
  - William Neal Moore, 1984; 1988 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 41)
  - Moore v. Southwestern Bell Telephone Co., 1979 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 42)
  - Moore's Ford Murder, 1972 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 43)
  - "Moratorium on the Death Penalty for Juveniles" by Victor Streib, 1988 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 44)
  - Morgan, 1989 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 45)
  - Morgan v. Florida -FLSC- Opinion, 1987 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 46)
  - Morris v. State, 1984 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 47)
  - "Mr.Justice Arthur J. Goldberg and the Death Penalty: A memorandum to the Conference" by Robert S. Marsel, 1986 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 48)
  - " Mr. Justice Black and the Judicial Function" by Paul A. Freund, 1967 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 49)
  - " Mr. Justice William Johnson and the Constitution" by Donald G. Morgan, 1944 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 50)
  - "Mr. Justice William Johnson and the Uneviable Dilemma" by A.J. Levin, 1944 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 51)
  - "Mr. Justice William Johnson, Creative Dissenter" by A.J. Levin, 1944 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 52)
  - "Mr. Justice William Johnson, Jurist in Limine" by A.J. Levin, 1948 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 53)
  - Murray v. Carrier, 1986 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 54)
  - Musgrove v. Alabama, 1982 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 55)
  - NAACP Legal Defense Fund - Capital Punishment Conference-List of Names, 1993 (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 56)
  - "Natural Law"- Naturalism in Ethics, Richard Walhelm, Undated (Box 10 (7-Research Files), Folder 57)
  - Bridging the Gap: Transitional Benefits- What are they? An Overview and Survey of 15 Countries, Undated (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 1)
  - " The Nature of Judicial Review" by Harry H. Wellington, 1982 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 2)
  - " The Nature of Precedent" by Earl Maltz, 1988 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - Nelson Textbook of Pediatrics, Twelfth Edition by Behram and Voughan- Excerpts, 1983 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - "Neuropsychiatric, Psychoeducational, and Family Characteristics of 14 Juveniles Condemned to Death in the United States" by Dorothy Ornow Lew, et al., 1988 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - " Neutral Principles in the 1950's" by Gary Peller, 1988 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - New Jersey v. J.Q., 1992 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - New Jesey v. Michaels, Undated (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - New Jersey v. Reed- Affadavit of Leigh Bienen, 1988 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - New Jersey v. T.L.O, 1985 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - New York v. Ferber, 1982 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 11)
  - New York v. McKiernan, 1994 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - New York v. Romer, 1992 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 13)
  - The New Yorker, 1990 March 12 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 14)
  - Newlon v. Armontrovt, 1989 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 15)
  - Newspaper Analysis, 1962; 1988; 1992-1994; 2002-2004; Undated (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 16)
  - "Non Occides: Thurgood Marshall and the Death Penalty" by William J. Daniels, 1977 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 17)
  - "Normative and Nowhere to Go" by Pierre Schlag, 1990 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 18)
  - Notes on Hitchcock Harmless Error Cases, 1990 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 19)
  - NYS Assembly-1995 Committee Bill Memorandum (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 20)
  - NYS Bills S.2850 and A.4843, 1995 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 21)
  - O'Callaghan v. State, 1989 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 22)
  - "Off the Pedestal and Onto the Block? Motherhood, Reproductive Technologies, and the Canadian State" by Somer Brodribb, 1986 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 23)
  - Old Race Statutes, 1822; 1828; 1830; 1832; 1840 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 24)
  - Old Race Statutes, 1847; 1850; 1865-1866; 1868; 1881 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 25)
  - Old Race Statutes, 1891; 1892; 1894; 1917; 1921 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 26)
  - Old Race Statutes, 1923; 1953; 1959; 1962-1963; 1966-1967 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 27)
  - Old Race Statutes, 1972; 1982; 1990; Undated (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 28)
  - "On Teaching Feminist Jurisprudence" by Liana Fiol Matta, 1988 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 29)
  - "On the Front Line: Law Enforcement Views on the Death Penalty" by Richard C. Dieter, 1995 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 30)
  - "On the Perils of Line- Drawing: Juveniles and the Death Penalty"- Joseph L. Hoffman, 1988 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 31)
  - Order of Supreme Court from the Supreme Court of Ohio Following Lockett v. Ohio, 1978 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 32)
  - Oregon v. Mitchell, 1970 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 33)
  - "Origins of the Unwritten Constitution: Fundemental Law in American Revolutionary Thought" by Thomas C. Grey, 1978 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 34)
  - Parham v. J.R., 1978 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 35)
  - " Passionate Scholarship: Notes on values, knowing and method in feminist social science" by Barbara DuBois, 1983 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 36)
  - "The Path of Law"- Justice Holmes, 1897 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 37)
  - "Patterns of Death: An Analysis of Racial Dispanties in Cultural Sentencing and Homicide Victimization" by Gross and Mauro, 1984 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 38)
  - Payne v. Virginia, 1986 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 39)
  - Pedrero v. Wainwright, 1979 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 40)
  - "Penal Sanctions as a Feminist Strategy: A Contradiction in Terms? Pornography and Criminal Law in Netherlands" by Brants and Kok, 1986 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 41)
  - Pennsylvania v. Finley, 1986-1987 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 42)
  - John Paul Penry, 1987-1988 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 43)
  - People v. Carpenter, 1992 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 44)
  - People v. Smith, 1984 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 45)
  - Percy v. Vermont, 1991 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 46)
  - Perkins v. Texas, 1994 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 47)
  - Persons Executed for Crimes Committed While Under Age Eighteen- Fifth Edition by Victor Streib, 1987 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 48)
  - Persons on Death Row as of June 24, 1988, for Crimes Committed While Under Age Eighteen by Victor Streib (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 49)
  - "Perspectives on Women's Subordination and the Role of Law" by Taub and Schneider, 1982 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 50)
  - Petition of James Terry Roach for Commutation of Sentence of Death, 1985 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 51)
  - Police Officers For Equal Rights v. City of Col., 1985 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 52)
  - Portia in a Different Voice: Speculations on a Women's Lawyering Process" By Carrie Menkel- Meadow, 1985 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 53)
  - Postconviction Remedies by Larry Yackle, 1990 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 54)
  - "Post- Furman Botched Executions" by Michael L. Radelet, 2004 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 55)
  - "Positivism and Fidelity to Law- A Reply to Professor Hart" by Lon L. Fuller, 1958 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 56)
  - "Positivism and the Separation of Law and Harris" by H.L.A. Hart, 1958 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 57)
  - Positivism, Utilitarianism, Natural Rights- The Idea of Justice, Undated (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 58)
  - Preston v. Florida, 1990 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 59)
  - Priestman v. US, 1800 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 60)
  - "A Prisoner's Constitutional Right to Attorney Assistence" by Raymond Y. Lin, 1983 (Box 11 (7-Research Files), Folder 61)
  - The Prisoners' Mail Box and the Evolution of Federal Inmate Rights by Ira P. Robbins, 1993 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 1)
  - "Pro Bono Representation of Death Sentenced Inmates" by John C. Godbold, 1987 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 2)
  - Proposed Amendment to CJA Plan for Southern District NY, 1992 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - Proposed Death Penalty Law in New York, 1994-1996 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - Proposed Grove City Legislation, Religious Liberty, and Private Education, 1986 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - Proposed Standards, 1995 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - Provenzano v. Dugger, 1990 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - "Psychiatric Problems of Adolescence" by Hunt and Cohen, 1983 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - The Psychology of Moral Development, Vol II by L. Kohlberg, 1984 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - Public Defender, Undated (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - Public Defense Services in Clinton County: An Assessment of the Assigned Counsel Program- Public Defense Backup Center, 1986 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 11)
  - Public Defense Services in New York State: Historical, Systemic, Case and Political Perspective by Jonathan E. Gradess, 1986 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - Public Defense Services in Ontario Country- Public Defense Backup Center, 1985 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 13)
  - Public Defense Services in Schenectaady County: An Assessment of the Assigned Counsel Program- Public Defense Backup Center, 1984 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 14)
  - Punitiveness and Public Opinion on Abortion and Capital Punishment in the United States by Kimberly Cook- Doctoral Dissertation ( 1 of 2), 1994 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 15)
  - Punitiveness and Public Opinion on Abortion and Capital Punishment in the United States by Kimberly Cook- Doctoral Dissertation ( 2 of 2), 1994 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 16)
  - Quarles v. Oxford Mun. Separate School Dist., 1989 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 17)
  - "Race and Death: The Judicial Evaluation of Evidence of Discrimination in Capital Sentencing" by Samuel R. Gross, 1985 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 18)
  - "Race, Racism, and Feminist Legal Theory" by Marke Kline, 1989 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 19)
  - James David Raulerson, 1982; 1985 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 20)
  - "Realism, Feminism, Methodology, and Law" by Maureen Cain, 1986 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 21)
  - "Realism, Nihilism, and the Supreme Court: Do the Emperors Have Nothing but Robes?" by John E. Nowak, 1983 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 22)
  - "A Realistic Jurisprudence- The Next Step" by Karl N. Llewellyn, 1930 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 23)
  - "Reason and Death" by George F. Will, 2003 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 24)
  - "Reason, Passian, and the Progress of the Law"-The 42nd Annual Bejamin N. Cardozo Lecture- By William J. Brennon, JR., 1988 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 25)
  - "Reasoning in the Personal and Moral Domains: Adolescent and Young Adult Women's Decision- Making Regarding Abortion" by Judith Smetana, 1981 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 26)
  - "Recent Public Opinion on the Juvenile Death Penalty"- Death Penalty Information Center, 2004 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 27)
  - Rector v. Clinton, 1992 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 28)
  - "Reflections on the Juvenile Death Penalty: Contravention of Precedent and Public Opinion" by Kim A. Lechner, 1997 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 29)
  - "Reflections on the significance of the sex /Gender System: Divorce Law Reform in New York" by Isabel Marcos, 1987 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 30)
  - Relentless Dissents- Research- Miscellaneous, 1815; 1940; 1987; 1989; 1991 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 31)
  - Remarks of the Chief Justice- American Bar Association Mid-Year Meeting, 1989 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 32)
  - "Remarks on the Death Penalty Made at the Judicial Conference of the Second Circuit" by Thurgood Marshall, 1986 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 33)
  - Report of the Florida Bar Commission to Study Practical Aspects of Death Sentence Appeals, 1991 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 34)
  - Representation of Indigent Defendants, 1954 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 35)
  - Representation of Indigent Defendants ( 1 of 2), 1959 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 36)
  - Representation of Indigent Defendants ( 2 of 2), 1959 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 37)
  - Representation of Indigent Defendants, 1961 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 38)
  - Representation of Indigent Defendants, 1962 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 39)
  - Representation of Parties, Undated (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 40)
  - "Reproductive Ethics: Feminist and Non-Feminist Approaches" by Christine Overall, 1986 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 41)
  - "The Requirement of Death: Mandatory Language in the Pennsylvania Death Penalty Statute" by Bruce S. Ledewitz, 1982 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 42)
  - "Re-Reading Contracts: A Feminist Analysis of Contracts Casebook" by Mary Joe Frug, 1985 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 43)
  - Review of Child Development Research, Volume one Edited by Hoffman and Hoffman- Excerpts, 1964 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 44)
  - "Right to Aid in Addition to Councel for Indigent Criminal Defendents", 1963 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 45)
  - "Right to Counsel in Criminal Post-Conviction Review Proceedings" by Gordon H. Van Kessel, 1963 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 46)
  - "The Right to Privacy" by Warren and Brandeis, 1890 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 47)
  - Riley v. Wainwright, 1987 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 48)
  - Risking the Future: Adolescent Sexuality, Pregnancy, and Childbearing, Volume I, Edited by Cheryl D. Hayes, 1987 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 49)
  - Ross v. Moffitt, 1974 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 50)
  - Ruffin v. Dugger, 1988 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 51)
  - S. 2455, 1988 (Box 12 (7-Research Files), Folder 52)
  - Saffle v. Parks, 1989 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 1)
  - Satterwhite v. Texas, 1988 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 2)
  - School v. Arizona, 1990 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 3)
  - Schall v. Martin, 1984 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 4)
  - Schlup v. Delo, 1993-1994 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 5)
  - "The Scope and Purpose of Sociological Jurisprudence" by Roscoe Pound, 1911 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 6)
  - "Section Seeks Volunteers to Represent Death Row Inmates" by Micael B Hyman, 1987 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 7)
  - Selvage v. Lynaugh, 1989 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 8)
  - Senate Bill 150: Death Penalty- Minors, 1988 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 9)
  - "Sexual Assault and the Feminist Judge" by Christine Boyle, 1985 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 10)
  - "Shorter Studies: Law and Morality" by John Kuhn Bleimaier, Undated (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 11)
  - Silagy v. Peters, 1990 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 12)
  - Simmons v. Luebbers, 2002 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 13)
  - Skipper v. South Carolina, 1986 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 14)
  - Smith v. Bounds, 1985 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 15)
  - "Social Injury Revisited: Towards a Feminist Theory of Social Justice" by Adrian Howe, 1987 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 16)
  - "Social Security Benefits: The Woman's Perspective" by Linda Tarr- Whelan, 1984 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 17)
  - " The Sociology of Law" by Philip Selznick, 1968 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 18)
  - "Some Realism About Critical Legal Studies" by Richard Michael Fischl, 1987 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 19)
  - "Some Realism about Realism- Responding to Dean Pound" by Karl N. Llewellyn, 1931 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 20)
  - "Some Thoughts about Natural Law" by Phillip E. Johnson, 1987 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 21)
  - "Some Thoughts on the Death of Stare Decisis in Constitutional Law" by Earl M. Maltz, 1980 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 22)
  - Carl Ray Songer, 1985 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 23)
  - Sonnier v. Maggio, 1993 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 24)
  - South Dakota v. Dole, 1986 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 25)
  - Southern California Law Review- Articles, 1985 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 26)
  - "The Spirit of Dissent" by J. Louis Campbell III, 1983 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 27)
  - Standards Relating to Juveniles Deliquency and Sactions - IJA- ABA Joint Commission on Juvenile Justices Standards, 1980 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 28)
  - Standing Alone in the Dock- Draft- A Report by the Death Penalty Information Center, ca. 1995 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 29)
  - Standing for First Time in US S. Ct., 1937; 1951; 1974; 1981 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 30)
  - Santo v. Barton, 1993 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 31)
  - "Stare Decisis, Dissent, and the Background of the Justices of the Supreme Court of the United States" by John R. Schmidhouser, 1962 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 32)
  - "The State as a Purveyor of Morality" by Don Welch, 1988 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 33)
  - State Execution Rates as of August 11, 2003, 2004 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 34)
  - State of California- Right to Serve on Jury, 2004 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 35)
  - Statement by the Honorable H. Lee Sarokin, 1993 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 36)
  - Statement of Federico M. Macias-Subcommitteee on Civil and Constitutionl Rights, 1993 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 37)
  - Statement of Kirk N. Bloodsworth- Subcommittee on Civil and Constitutional Rights, ca. 1993 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 38)
  - Statement of Justice Barkett FLSC- Hearing on Habeus Corpus Reform, 1991 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 39)
  - Statement of Rubin Carter- Hearing on Habeas Corpus, 1993 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 40)
  - Statement of Talbot D' Alemoente-Innocence and the Death Penalty, 1993 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 41)
  - "The Status of Capital Punishment: A World Perspective" by Clarence H. Patrick, 1965 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 42)
  - Stewart v. Dugger, 1987-1988 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 43)
  - Strickland v. Washington, 1984 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 44)
  - Studies by Kathleen M. Heide, 1982; 1984; Undated (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 45)
  - A Study of Representation of Capital Cases in Texas- The Spangenberg Group, 1993 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 46)
  - "Style and Justice Holmes" by William Domnarksi, 1986 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 47)
  - Suarez v. Dugger, 1988 (Box 13 (7-Research Files), Folder 48)